男人啊可不能怂
刚才看的那么起劲
怎么我一说你就不敢看了
对不起我真的不是故意偷看的
好了我不逗你了
你多大了呀
还这么害羞
呃我叫张峰
今年23岁
刚从大学毕业
23 那跟姐姐也差不了多少吗
我啊比你大三岁哦
媚姐我还以为你跟我差不多大呢
这个小嘴还挺甜的
怎么样有没有女朋友了呀
那介不介意姐姐当你女朋友呀
俗话说的好吗
女大三
不是媚姐你说笑了说笑了
看把你吓得
也是我嫁过人
你怎么能看得上我呢
嫁过人
结婚那天前夫他是喝个烂醉
回到房里倒头就是呼呼大睡
第二天一早说是上山弄点野味
没想到他和我公公被那野猪来追
追呀追呀追
野猪跑的也挺累
一气之下把他们两人顶飞
Men can't be cowardly
I just looked so excited
Why don't you dare to watch it when I say it?
Sorry, I really didn't mean to peek.
Ok I won't tease you
How old are you?
Still so shy
Uh, my name is Zhang Feng.
I am 23 years old.
Just graduated from college
23 Is that not much different from my sister?
I am three years older than you.
Sister Mei, I thought you were about the same age as me
This little mouth is pretty sweet
How is it? Do you have a girlfriend?
Do you mind if my sister is your girlfriend?
As the saying goes
Female junior
It's not Sister Mei, you're joking, joking
Look, it scares you.
I was also married
How can you like me?
married
On the wedding day, his ex-husband was drunk
I went back to my room and fell asleep.
The next morning, it was said to go up the mountain to get some game.
I didn't expect him and my father-in-law to be chased by the wild boar
Chase, chase, chase
The wild boar is also tired from running
In a fit of rage, the two of them flew